I'm a Lutheran so yeah oh yeah we're
booth I have a lot of bad habits I have
a lot of vices mainly lutefisk and
pickled herring I'm real sorry about
that
don't come buy me another another bad
Lutheran Vice is the worst watered down
weakest coffee you ever had in your life
uh and that's why there are so many
Mormons that they tried the basement
Lutheran coffee and they're like no
we're going Mormon yeah okay see know
your audience
Wow I have two degrees in clarinet so
yeah that's why I do comedy
a clarinet never comes in handy for
anything unless maybe you're driving and
then you hit a deer and you don't have a
crowbar in your trunk to put it out of
its misery Wow
last time I hit a deer I had my clarinet
with me and I only got through like two
songs and he was out
yeah that's that's how good I am
my first job was that actually beginning
band teacher that's what I did yeah
[Applause]
no that is the job from a Qi double
hockey sticks I mean it to I think like
somebody went bound to hell and scooped
up some of the molten material and
brought it back and cooled it off is
that behold flutes and recorders ah do
you remember the recorders oh oh that
little plastic whistle you think it's
plastic it's genuine hell fire brimstone
yeah and every time you play the
recorder it calls the devil
yeah yeah yeah and then the devil is
like god crap I gotta go up there and
hear hot cross buns again if there ever
anything to make all the dark forces in
the world repent it'd be 30 elementary
kids playing hot cross bun on recorder
for three months you know and when
you're a teacher first-year teacher you
have such high hopes you're like yeah
kids for the holiday program this year
we're gonna play something from
Beethoven's 9th yeah by the third year
you're like okay you little turds I'm
pretty sure this year we're just gonna
play jingle bells and we're gonna go
ahead and play it again for the spring
concert
strive to drive our comedy for even more
of the world's largest collection of
clean comedy